Bryce, congrats on being drafted.
Welcome to Indianapolis.
What interaction did you have if any
with the Colts throughout the pre-draft
process and what do you think you can
bring to this football team?
Yeah, I'd say number one it started at
the Senior Bowl. Coach June was my
linebacker coach there.
You know, and that was awesome. I love
Coach June. You know, very cerebral when
it comes to the game and a great, you
know, motivator. So, I'd say it started
there and then obviously at the combine
I interviewed with them.
And hopped on a Zoom call with
Coach Betcher which shares my last name
as a matter of fact, so that was pretty
damn cool as well.
Abby, go ahead.
Bryce, congratulations. This is not the
first draft you've been a part of. You
were an MLB draft selection just a
couple years ago. How do the emotions
compare this time around? And what is it
How has it been different for you this
time?
Yeah, I'd say number one
was probably just the selection process
like in the interview process. Baseball,
I mean, obviously have an interview
process, but it's not as in-depth. The
NFL definitely dive takes a deep dive, a
lot of interviews.
I think granted, you know, there's a
longer time period that they have to
interview.
But I'd say number one is just more
in-depth.
Nathan.
Hey Bryce.
I know you obviously after you got
selected by the Astros a couple years
ago in the 13th round, you made that
decision to continue to pursue football
and that's continued for for 2 years
now. What has driven that
priority on on wanting to continue to
push toward the NFL
and
you know, and and see what you can do
with Colts?
No doubt. I'd say number one was just my
love for the game. You know, I love
baseball, but football's definitely my
passion.
I grew up playing, you know, all
different sports, but there's no better
feeling than, you know, kind of
inflicting pain on someone legally
and the bond you develop with your
teammates throughout the process. So,
I'd say just the game of football itself
and how much love I had for the game was
why I chose to keep playing it.
Jake, go ahead.
Hey Bryce. I I talked to you briefly
down at the Senior Bowl actually.
One thing we discussed was you've always
been kind of lauded for your leadership.
You've obviously been there at Oregon
for a while.
You caught on as a leader there in in
Mobile as well. I I know that was one
thing a lot of the guys complimented
about you.
What is the value of that and like
have you thought [clears throat] about
that yet at all when it comes to the
NFL? Like you're going into a locker
room with a bunch of veterans. That's
always been kind of a big part of your
orbit, you know, in a program.
Yeah, I mean, obviously leadership is a
big big part of me, but I'd say number
one is just leading by example. You
know, I got to showcase that to my peers
that I'm willing to do
everything first before I ask anything
of them.
Now, you know, once you you know,
develop that respect and you get to know
people off the field, you're able to be
a vocal leader which I take pride in as
well.
But yeah, both both pieces are, you
know, things that I that I have in my,
you know, ability.
We'll do a few more. Fox 59, go ahead.
Bryce, congratulations. Obviously, the
Colts had another prolific Oregon Duck
in DeForest Buckner. What Just what
excites you about the chance to play
with him?
Man, I grew up watching DeForest Buckner
play.
Being from the area, you know, I had
season tickets to all the games and that
was a dude that, you know, when I was
11, 12 years old I'm watching that dude
play, you know, on Saturdays and I'll
get a chance to play with him on
Sundays. So, you know, I'm excited to
get to meet him
and learn from him.
We'll go with Nathan and then Trap will
be our last question.
Hey Bryce, just another question for you
on being a two-sport athlete. I know you
played center field and a couple more
spots when you were on the baseball
field a couple years ago. What In what
way do you feel like going so deep in
two sports
helped you as a linebacker on the
football field in these two kind of
breakout seasons that you had in Oregon
the last couple seasons?
Yeah, that's a good question, man.
I'd say number one would probably be
just a willingness to see something
happen and go for it. You know, no
questions asked. Like in center field
when you see a ball hit, you got to
react and go full speed to the spot to
make the play. If you second-guess
yourself or hesitate, you're not going
to make the play.
And I'd say that's, you know, hand in
hand with football. You know, you see
the running back take the ball and hit a
hit a gap, you got to go. You can't
second-guess yourself. So, I'd say
that's number one. And number two would
just be overall work ethic. There was a
lot of times where I was going to two
practices a day, you know, not really
knowing, you know, if I was going to get
my opportunity, but I just kept sticking
with it. And I think that just kind of
grind mentality stuck with me throughout
this football process.
Trap, go ahead.
Yeah, Bryce, I'm curious. In baseball,
you can't legally legally inflict pain
on people.
Have you ever thought about what your
future would have been like in baseball?
I mean, legit.
Yeah, no, I certainly have. That was
definitely something I thought about
when I got drafted in 24. Um
Yeah, no, I think
I mean, I think I would have been a big
leaguer in baseball as well.
But I just I like the game of football
you know, a little bit better and that's
obviously my opportunity to Oregon, you
know, took me to a couple couple years
further past the Astros.
So, yeah, no, I thought about it, but
you know, my my future's football right
now and I'm excited to, you know, see
where that goes for me.
One quick follow-up. I assume you're a
Mike.
Yes, sir. I mean, I can play Mike, Will,
Sam, but I like having the green dot.
Yes, sir. Special teams?
Of course, yep.